{
    "id": "ea756b7f87c64912a2840409bb165720",
    "title": "Intermediate Level Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There is no ............................... in talking to him.",
            "description": "The correct expression is no point in.",
            "answers": [
                "point",
                "worth",
                "use"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "df5ae0af58e6435dadd6157046516f4a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The rain played havoc ............................... our plans.",
            "description": "The correction expression is play havoc with.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3b42508fedba410f92f974c20a2aea05"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................. all I know, she is still in love with him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "For",
                "As",
                "With"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f646444729c942c69c433e97fb4ade65"
        },
        {
            "question": "I look forward .................................... you.",
            "description": "The correct expression is look forward to + ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "to meet",
                "for meeting",
                "to meeting"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "056b0c6a6ad34baeb6c7aa3068995347"
        },
        {
            "question": "I told you ................................... me.",
            "description": "We make the negative form of the infinitive by putting not before to.",
            "answers": [
                "to not touch",
                "not to touch",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "97900da42d564cbc86f8a4582cae8926"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................. the time we reach there, the train will have left.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "By",
                "In",
                "After"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0d6a20f5a2714c9496e43d3490b264fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "Time .................................. all wounds.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "heals",
                "cures",
                "remedies"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7befbb7971fb44f18e70314754694fcd"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can't believe how .................................. I am.",
            "description": "When you are out of shape, you are in a very bad condition.",
            "answers": [
                "out of order",
                "out of shape",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "116fedd21cd140a6820dd95fb130d181"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had to wash the clothes by hand because the washing machine was ....................................",
            "description": "If a machine is out of order, it is not working.",
            "answers": [
                "out of shape",
                "out of order",
                "out of condition"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c9336b1796674213b0fa35c18b02d386"
        },
        {
            "question": "They burst ................................. tears after losing the championship.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "out into",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e1a97c8825b5458caf2426951aefbdc4"
        },
        {
            "question": "We reached on time .................................... the rain.",
            "description": "In spite of is a preposition. It is used before a noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "however",
                "in spite of",
                "although"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9d4c3e28eb654c2ea726459e15b7968c"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................. having a cold, I managed to enjoy the party.",
            "description": "We use despite before a noun or an ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "Despite",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2f768203545947a8a416e083e1c11900"
        }
    ]
}